[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Do you ever think we'd be sitting here by the pool of the Beverly Hilton doing an interview about your Oscar nomination?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "think", "we", "'d", "be", "sitting", "here", "by", "the", "pool", "of", "the", "Beverly", "Hilton", "doing", "an", "interview", "about", "your", "Oscar", "nomination", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Beverly Hilton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "And to be Oscar nominated, what is that mean to you as an artist?", "question_tokens": ["And", "to", "be", "Oscar", "nominated", ",", "what", "is", "that", "mean", "to", "you", "as", "an", "artist", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "You know, its an honor, it's a thrill all of the above.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "its", "an", "honor", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "thrill", "all", "of", "the", "above", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "Are you going to pretend like everybody else I've interviewed that you haven't written a winner's speech yet?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "going", "to", "pretend", "like", "everybody", "else", "I", "'ve", "interviewed", "that", "you", "have", "n't", "written", "a", "winner", "'s", "speech", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "Who when you really think about it that you personally most thankful too?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "when", "you", "really", "think", "about", "it", "that", "you", "personally", "most", "thankful", "too", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "JJS", "JJ", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "I mean this instance it will be one person.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "this", "instance", "it", "will", "be", "one", "person", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Arch"]}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 71, "question": "Was he the greatest figure of your lifetime?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "the", "greatest", "figure", "of", "your", "lifetime", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Well, you know, he and his mate, his neighbor, the Arch, as they call him ...", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "he", "and", "his", "mate", ",", "his", "neighbor", ",", "the", "Arch", ",", "as", "they", "call", "him", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "CC", "VBN", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "What would your mother have made of you of the Oscars?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "your", "mother", "have", "made", "of", "you", "of", "the", "Oscars", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Well, she only saw or heard me sing once and on the stage just before she passed away.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "she", "only", "saw", "or", "heard", "me", "sing", "once", "and", "on", "the", "stage", "just", "before", "she", "passed", "away", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bono"]}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "That's what you're missing and defiance is the essence of romance, isn't it Piers?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "what", "you", "'re", "missing", "and", "defiance", "is", "the", "essence", "of", "romance", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "It certainly is, Bono.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "certainly", "is", ",", "Bono", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 94, "question": "If I had the power to let you relive one moment in your life outside of marriage and children, which one would you choose?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "had", "the", "power", "to", "let", "you", "relive", "one", "moment", "in", "your", "life", "outside", "of", "marriage", "and", "children", ",", "which", "one", "would", "you", "choose", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "CD", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "CD", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 95, "answer": "Gosh.", "answer_tokens": ["Gosh", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ":", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "What's the one -- what's the one if I said, I can -- you can have that again tonight?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "one", "--", "what", "'s", "the", "one", "if", "I", "said", ",", "I", "can", "--", "you", "can", "have", "that", "again", "tonight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", ":", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "MD", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "Playing on stage for that time in front of all of my school friends and indeed my mother in the audience if you asked because that bond (inaudible).", "answer_tokens": ["Playing", "on", "stage", "for", "that", "time", "in", "front", "of", "all", "of", "my", "school", "friends", "and", "indeed", "my", "mother", "in", "the", "audience", "if", "you", "asked", "because", "that", "bond", "(", "inaudible", ")", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 103, "question": "Finally, did you ever find what you're looking for?", "question_tokens": ["Finally", ",", "did", "you", "ever", "find", "what", "you", "'re", "looking", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "Did I finally found what I'm looking for ...", "answer_tokens": ["Did", "I", "finally", "found", "what", "I", "'m", "looking", "for", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "Is it Vivienne Westwood again?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "Vivienne", "Westwood", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Vivienne Westwood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Bono"]}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "Can you do that?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "do", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "I don't know any -- I don't think anyone can take down Bono.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "any", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "anyone", "can", "take", "down", "Bono", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "So what's happens?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "'s", "happens", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "POS", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "None of those views are mine.", "answer_tokens": ["None", "of", "those", "views", "are", "mine", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", ":"], "qSentId": 189, "question": "That moment if you win and you go the Oscars podium, who will you feel most thankful to in your life for helping bring you to that moment?", "question_tokens": ["That", "moment", "if", "you", "win", "and", "you", "go", "the", "Oscars", "podium", ",", "who", "will", "you", "feel", "most", "thankful", "to", "in", "your", "life", "for", "helping", "bring", "you", "to", "that", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJS", "JJ", "TO", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "That's the thing, it's like asking ...", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "the", "thing", ",", "it", "'s", "like", "asking", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "DT", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 192, "question": "In that moment if you won, when you look back at your entire life who will you feel most thankful to?", "question_tokens": ["In", "that", "moment", "if", "you", "won", ",", "when", "you", "look", "back", "at", "your", "entire", "life", "who", "will", "you", "feel", "most", "thankful", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJS", "JJ", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 193, "answer": "Definitely the omniscient because that's where it all comes from.", "answer_tokens": ["Definitely", "the", "omniscient", "because", "that", "'s", "where", "it", "all", "comes", "from", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "And who down here?", "question_tokens": ["And", "who", "down", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "There's a long list of people who got me to where I am right now.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "a", "long", "list", "of", "people", "who", "got", "me", "to", "where", "I", "am", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "When you're standing there potentially is an Oscar winner, who will come in to your head?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "'re", "standing", "there", "potentially", "is", "an", "Oscar", "winner", ",", "who", "will", "come", "in", "to", "your", "head", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "So many faces.", "answer_tokens": ["So", "many", "faces", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "Any family?", "question_tokens": ["Any", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "My mom and my Dad for sure.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "mom", "and", "my", "Dad", "for", "sure", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", ":", "DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Which moment would be the greatest moment of you life so far?", "question_tokens": ["Which", "moment", "would", "be", "the", "greatest", "moment", "of", "you", "life", "so", "far", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "ILLIAMS: I couldn't because all of these things are -- every second is a piece in the mosaic for this moment.", "answer_tokens": ["ILLIAMS", ":", "I", "could", "n't", "because", "all", "of", "these", "things", "are", "--", "every", "second", "is", "a", "piece", "in", "the", "mosaic", "for", "this", "moment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 209, "question": "You can do it all over again?", "question_tokens": ["You", "can", "do", "it", "all", "over", "again", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 210, "answer": "When I first met my wife.", "answer_tokens": ["When", "I", "first", "met", "my", "wife", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Alex"]}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", ":", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "When was that?", "question_tokens": ["When", "was", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Over my buddy Alex's house down in a -- down in (inaudible).", "answer_tokens": ["Over", "my", "buddy", "Alex", "'s", "house", "down", "in", "a", "--", "down", "in", "(", "inaudible", ")", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 215, "question": "And how am I going to land her?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "am", "I", "going", "to", "land", "her", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "NN", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "."], "aSentId": 216, "answer": "I knew it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "knew", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "How do you feel about this extraordinary resurgence?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "this", "extraordinary", "resurgence", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "It doesn't feel surreal I mean it feels very real it's happening, and I understand what's happening, I'm aware of what's happening.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "does", "n't", "feel", "surreal", "I", "mean", "it", "feels", "very", "real", "it", "'s", "happening", ",", "and", "I", "understand", "what", "'s", "happening", ",", "I", "'m", "aware", "of", "what", "'s", "happening", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "I tweeted the other day, are you on Twitter?", "question_tokens": ["I", "tweeted", "the", "other", "day", ",", "are", "you", "on", "Twitter", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", ":", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 286, "question": "Is that the key?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "key", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 287, "answer": "That's -- yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "--", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "TO", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Who are the key people when you look back over the whole time that you would feel most thankful to?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "are", "the", "key", "people", "when", "you", "look", "back", "over", "the", "whole", "time", "that", "you", "would", "feel", "most", "thankful", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBS", "JJ", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "Well, I've got thanks -- I've got my own personal thanks to God, I've got my own personal thanks to family in many respects, the family I've got now, the family I came from, and I've got another little secret thank for somebody I know very well that I might share if I was so fortunate to.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'ve", "got", "thanks", "--", "I", "'ve", "got", "my", "own", "personal", "thanks", "to", "God", ",", "I", "'ve", "got", "my", "own", "personal", "thanks", "to", "family", "in", "many", "respects", ",", "the", "family", "I", "'ve", "got", "now", ",", "the", "family", "I", "came", "from", ",", "and", "I", "'ve", "got", "another", "little", "secret", "thank", "for", "somebody", "I", "know", "very", "well", "that", "I", "might", "share", "if", "I", "was", "so", "fortunate", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "RB", ":"], "qSentId": 303, "question": "What do you think you'll feel when you're standing there if you get that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "you", "'ll", "feel", "when", "you", "'re", "standing", "there", "if", "you", "get", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "Well, I'm not -- I'm -- look, I'm not there yet so ...", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "--", "I", "'m", "--", "look", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "there", "yet", "so", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "But if you do, how would you feel?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "you", "do", ",", "how", "would", "you", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "... I really haven't thought about what I would feel.", "answer_tokens": ["...", "I", "really", "have", "n't", "thought", "about", "what", "I", "would", "feel", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "Replay that -- just any moment?", "question_tokens": ["Replay", "that", "--", "just", "any", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", ":", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Any moment.", "answer_tokens": ["Any", "moment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 322, "question": "The greatest moment?", "question_tokens": ["The", "greatest", "moment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 323, "answer": "One you'd most like to live through again.", "answer_tokens": ["One", "you", "'d", "most", "like", "to", "live", "through", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 330, "question": "What impact did that have on you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "impact", "did", "that", "have", "on", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 331, "answer": "CCONAUGHEY: Courage, integrity, you know, anybody loses a father that's the main crutch in a man's life, and he's there for a reason because, you know, if it ever comes down to it you got, you know, my father would lean up against me.", "answer_tokens": ["CCONAUGHEY", ":", "Courage", ",", "integrity", ",", "you", "know", ",", "anybody", "loses", "a", "father", "that", "'s", "the", "main", "crutch", "in", "a", "man", "'s", "life", ",", "and", "he", "'s", "there", "for", "a", "reason", "because", ",", "you", "know", ",", "if", "it", "ever", "comes", "down", "to", "it", "you", "got", ",", "you", "know", ",", "my", "father", "would", "lean", "up", "against", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "So what's your father have made of you being Oscar nominee?", "question_tokens": ["So", "what", "'s", "your", "father", "have", "made", "of", "you", "being", "Oscar", "nominee", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "POS", "PRP$", "NN", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "He'd love it.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'d", "love", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "Can you quite believe it?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "quite", "believe", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Mexico"]}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "How I can lose 43 pounds quickly?", "question_tokens": ["How", "I", "can", "lose", "43", "pounds", "quickly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "Go to Mexico and drink the water.", "answer_tokens": ["Go", "to", "Mexico", "and", "drink", "the", "water", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Merry, how does that feel?", "question_tokens": ["Merry", ",", "how", "does", "that", "feel", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "It feels so incredible.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "feels", "so", "incredible", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "Do you two, do you prefer to backing singers or has the dream always been, Merry, to be center stage yourself?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "two", ",", "do", "you", "prefer", "to", "backing", "singers", "or", "has", "the", "dream", "always", "been", ",", "Merry", ",", "to", "be", "center", "stage", "yourself", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CD", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBN", ",", "NNP", ",", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "LAYTON: Well, you know, when I was singing background I always felt like I was center stage.", "answer_tokens": ["LAYTON", ":", "Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "when", "I", "was", "singing", "background", "I", "always", "felt", "like", "I", "was", "center", "stage", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Merry"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 426, "question": "How do you feel when you see that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "when", "you", "see", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 427, "answer": "I was just so young.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "just", "so", "young", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 462, "question": "The kind of moment like that where you hear Stevie Wonder or Ray Charles or whoever it maybe bestowing that kind of comment, that honor on you?", "question_tokens": ["The", "kind", "of", "moment", "like", "that", "where", "you", "hear", "Stevie", "Wonder", "or", "Ray", "Charles", "or", "whoever", "it", "maybe", "bestowing", "that", "kind", "of", "comment", ",", "that", "honor", "on", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "JJR", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 463, "answer": "Well, it was so unexpected.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "was", "so", "unexpected", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ray Charles"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 472, "question": "Are you kidding?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "kidding", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 473, "answer": "Is it -- you've been Oscar-nominated because love the idea ...", "answer_tokens": ["Is", "it", "--", "you", "'ve", "been", "Oscar-nominated", "because", "love", "the", "idea", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJR", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "Do you feel a little bit of \"why not me\"?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "a", "little", "bit", "of", "``", "why", "not", "me", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "``", "WRB", "RB", "PRP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Well, as I said earlier, it was always me.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "as", "I", "said", "earlier", ",", "it", "was", "always", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "It was always me, you know, I mean if I'm giving my heart as I said in the film and my soul to your project, I come in -- excuse me, can I say this?", "question_tokens": ["It", "was", "always", "me", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "mean", "if", "I", "'m", "giving", "my", "heart", "as", "I", "said", "in", "the", "film", "and", "my", "soul", "to", "your", "project", ",", "I", "come", "in", "--", "excuse", "me", ",", "can", "I", "say", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "NN", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "Do you -- let me ask you one thing before we get another break?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "--", "let", "me", "ask", "you", "one", "thing", "before", "we", "get", "another", "break", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "CD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 520, "question": "Do you ever have, either of you, do ever have big stars, you don't have to name them if you don't want to, have asked you not to sing too well so you don't eclipse them?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "ever", "have", ",", "either", "of", "you", ",", "do", "ever", "have", "big", "stars", ",", "you", "do", "n't", "have", "to", "name", "them", "if", "you", "do", "n't", "want", "to", ",", "have", "asked", "you", "not", "to", "sing", "too", "well", "so", "you", "do", "n't", "eclipse", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", ",", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 521, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "What did you mean by that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "mean", "by", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "I think that what I meant is background singing is such an awesome thing and you can really get into it and you learn from so many different people.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "what", "I", "meant", "is", "background", "singing", "is", "such", "an", "awesome", "thing", "and", "you", "can", "really", "get", "into", "it", "and", "you", "learn", "from", "so", "many", "different", "people", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "CD", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "What is that X factor, for one of the better phrase that takes you from being just a singer to being a star do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "that", "X", "factor", ",", "for", "one", "of", "the", "better", "phrase", "that", "takes", "you", "from", "being", "just", "a", "singer", "to", "being", "a", "star", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "RB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Well, you know, Piers, I'm still trying to figure that one out and I mean for so many years you work with all these great, great people and they won't do it without you.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "'m", "still", "trying", "to", "figure", "that", "one", "out", "and", "I", "mean", "for", "so", "many", "years", "you", "work", "with", "all", "these", "great", ",", "great", "people", "and", "they", "wo", "n't", "do", "it", "without", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ray Charles"], "LOCATION": ["Carnegie Hall"]}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "What's has been the moment if I could say you could relive it right now?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "has", "been", "the", "moment", "if", "I", "could", "say", "you", "could", "relive", "it", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "Mine was the moment that I worked with Ray Charles in Carnegie Hall.", "answer_tokens": ["Mine", "was", "the", "moment", "that", "I", "worked", "with", "Ray", "Charles", "in", "Carnegie", "Hall", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "140214pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "``", "PRP", "RB", "NNP", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "''", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "TO", "NN", "PRP", "``", "DT", "NNP", "''", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 627, "question": "Judith, what would yours be?", "question_tokens": ["Judith", ",", "what", "would", "yours", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 628, "answer": "Definitely singing with Michael \"I Just Can't Stop Loving You\", the duet and to sing him \"This Close\" that was definitely the pinch me moment.", "answer_tokens": ["Definitely", "singing", "with", "Michael", "``", "I", "Just", "Ca", "n't", "Stop", "Loving", "You", "''", ",", "the", "duet", "and", "to", "sing", "him", "``", "This", "Close", "''", "that", "was", "definitely", "the", "pinch", "me", "moment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Judith"]}}]